{
  "0":[
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950658",
    "correctAnswer": "Anthony Quinn",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James Hong",
      "Gary Cooper",
      "Sam Shepard"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Lawrence of Arabia and La Strada?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625fd64ddc0dd3b72da64ce6",
    "correctAnswer": "1972",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1954",
      "1960",
      "1966"
    ],
    "question": "In which year was The Godfather released?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950668",
    "correctAnswer": "Dennis Hopper",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tim Roth",
      "Hugo Weaving",
      "Warwick Davis"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Apocalypse Now and Speed?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa83",
    "correctAnswer": "Christopher Walken",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bruce Dern",
      "Richard Farnsworth",
      "John Hurt"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 1978 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for playing the role of Nick in The Deer Hunter?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "cult_films",
      "academy_awards",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506a3",
    "correctAnswer": "Melissa Leo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Naomi Watts",
      "Keira Knightley",
      "Kristin Scott Thomas"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Cold Case and Veronica Mars?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501e0",
    "correctAnswer": "Sidney Lumet",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ],
    "question": "Which director directed 12 Angry Men?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950674",
    "correctAnswer": "Jack Lemmon",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timothy Spall",
      "Hugo Weaving",
      "Tim Roth"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Some Like It Hot and JFK?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa6e",
    "correctAnswer": "Morgan Freeman",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alan Alda",
      "Thomas Haden Church",
      "Jamie Foxx"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 2004 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for playing the role of Eddie Scrap-Iron Dupris in Million Dollar Baby?",
    "tags": [
      "academy_awards",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "63dd25e3742e43ed64f1f040",
    "correctAnswer": "Niles Crane",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frasier Moon",
      "Roz Doyle",
      "Martin Crane"
    ],
    "question": "What is the name of the character played by David Hyde Pierce on the show 'Frasier'?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv",
      "tv",
      "sitcoms"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa65",
    "correctAnswer": "Christoph Waltz",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Alan Arkin",
      "Robert De Niro",
      "Philip Seymour Hoffman"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 2012 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for playing the role of Dr. King Schultz in Django Unchained?",
    "tags": [
      "academy_awards",
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc46",
    "correctAnswer": "\"You talking to me?\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"It's alive! It's alive!\"",
      "\"Attica! Attica!\"",
      "\"After all, tomorrow is another day!\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Taxi Driver'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fad6",
    "correctAnswer": "Roberto Benigni",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tom Hanks",
      "Ian McKellen",
      "Nick Nolte"
    ],
    "question": "Who won the 1998 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Guido in Life Is Beautiful?",
    "tags": [
      "academy_awards",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625740af9da29df7b05f73f0",
    "correctAnswer": "After he becomes a quadriplegic, an aristocrat hires a young man to be his caregiver.",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "A naive youth leader is appointed to fill a vacancy in the U.S. Senate.",
      "An archaeologist is hired by the government to find the Ark of the Covenant.",
      "When a serial killer murders key political figures, a vigilante is forced to intervene."
    ],
    "question": "What is the plot of the movie Untouchable?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95065d",
    "correctAnswer": "Timothy Spall",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Paul Newman",
      "Tobey Maguire",
      "Dennis Hopper"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire and Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
    "tags": [
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbf5",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Cinderella story. Outta nowhere. A former greenskeeper, now, about to become the Masters champion. It looks like a mirac...It's in the hole! It's in the hole! It's in the hole!\"",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "\"As God is my witness, I'll never be hungry again.\"",
      "\"Open the pod bay doors, please, HAL.\"",
      "\"Oh, Jerry, don't let's ask for the moon. We have the stars.\""
    ],
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Caddyshack'?",
    "tags": [
      "quotes",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9505e4",
    "correctAnswer": "Kenneth Branagh",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Michael Ironside",
      "Luke Evans",
      "Tom Waits"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featured in films including Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets and Dunkirk?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950786",
    "correctAnswer": "Ben Affleck",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Keanu Reeves",
      "Donald Sutherland",
      "Christian Bale"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor played the role of Batman in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice and Justice League?",
    "tags": [
      "actors",
      "film",
      "dc",
      "comics",
      "film_and_tv",
      "batman"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95067f",
    "correctAnswer": "Paul Newman",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tim Roth",
      "Hugo Weaving",
      "Warwick Davis"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including The Sting and The Towering Inferno?",
    "tags": [
      "acting",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "625fd672dc0dd3b72da64cf1",
    "correctAnswer": "1975",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "1970",
      "1980",
      "1985"
    ],
    "question": "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest was released in which year?",
    "tags": [
      "film",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950667",
    "correctAnswer": "Warwick Davis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Timothy Spall",
      "Jack Lemmon",
      "Paul Newman"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Rogue One and Return of the Jedi?",
    "tags": [
      "star_wars",
      "film_and_tv"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]
}